organicliaison.com 2013-04-20

# Organic Liaison

Organic Liaison, LLC, is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing an Organic Liaison website, you acknowledge, fully understand, and agree to be bound by Organic Liaison’s Privacy Policy, and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this website Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Organic Liaison online. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g., message board, blog, personal page, etc.), or for the privacy practices of websites that are operated or owned by third parties.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and therefore encourage you to revisit this page periodically or when you notice new features or products on this website.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU

Organic Liaison collects two types of information:

  * personally identifiable information, and
  * non-personally identifiable information, which are more explained below.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

You are free to visit and use our Website without providing any personal information about yourself. However, Organic Liaison offers products and services on this website that require registration and/or the submission of personal information. Such personal information may include your name, address, email address, phone number and, if you are making a purchase of goods or services, your billing and credit card information. You acknowledge and agree that when you provide Organic Liaison with personal information you are doing so voluntarily.

Instances in which we might collect personal information on you include, but are not limited to:

  * when you register for the website or a user account;
  * when you register for, or elect to receive, email notifications, updates, newsletters, or other communications from Organic Liaison; or
  * when you participate in contests, sweepstakes, promotions or surveys on or through this website.

#### Non-personally Identifiable Information

If you choose to use this website without registering or submitting any personal information, then the only information we will collect from you is general non-personal information. Such non-personally identifiable information may include such demographic data as age, profession, gender, height, weight, etc. We may also collect non-personally identifiable technical information such as user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of this website.

We may use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and log files to track non personal information about visitors to this website in the aggregate. This non personal, aggregate data is used to analyze trends, to track user movement around this website, and to gather demographic information about how members, subscribers, and/or visitors use our website.

In some cases, when you click on a link or an advertisement in an email or newsletter you may receive from us, your browser may be momentarily directed to the site of a third party which, acting on Organic Liaison's behalf, notes or "counts" your response to the email or newsletter before re-directing your browser to its proper destination. This re-direction process will not be apparent to you. Your personal information will not be recorded by this third party.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on our website to determine the number of unique visitors, to personalize your online experience, to identify returning visitors, and to provide you with advertisements and messages of interest to you. Organic Liaison does not store any personal information in any cookies on your computer. However, we do link the non-personal information we store in cookies to your personal information.

Also, companies offering products or services through this website may use their own cookies. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use or placement of cookies by any third party.

Your browser may be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookie(s), you will be restricted to certain free areas of our website and will be unable to access areas of the website available to paid members.

We may also use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit this website. This company may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Web Beacons**

Our third party advertising partners may employ a software technology called clear gifs that help us to validate sales on this website. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. In contrast to cookies which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the non-personal information gathered by clear gifs to your personal information, and we do not use clear gifs to collect any personal information from or about you or to track your activities across websites generally.

**Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may use this information (which does not identify individual users) to analyze trends, to administer this website, and to identify and solve hardware and software problems as they arise. We may link this automatically-collected data to your personal information for the purpose of determining your interests and to offer you goods or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

#### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, Organic Liaison will not disclose any personal information it gathers from you on this website without your prior permission. In some circumstances, we must disclose your personal information to third parties who help us administer this website or our services. These third parties are required to keep your information confidential and do not use your information for any purpose other than the purpose under which your information was collected. Additionally, we may offer the goods or services of third parties on this website. If you should make a purchase from a third party seller, we will have to disclose your personal information to these third parties so that your order can be placed and processed. We may also release personal information to third parties to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, court order, or legal process; or in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others; or to protect the rights and/or property of Organic Liaison. Additionally, in the unlikely event that the entirety of our business is sold, liquidated, merged, or transferred to a third party, we may transfer all personal and non-personal information to the party purchasing or merging with us.

**Disclosure to Third Parties Generally**

Occasionally we may invite you to be contacted by third parties whose goods or services may be of interest to you. We will only share your personal information with these third parties if you grant us permission to do so. Furthermore, we may provide third parties with non-personal information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of this website. For example, we provide our advertisers and other third parties with aggregate, non-personal information about our website users, the number of users, their demographic information or user website activities.

**Disclosure to Outside Contractors**

We may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers to provide specific services and products related to this website, including but not limited to maintaining an email suppression list as required by state and/or federal law; hosting and maintaining our chat rooms; providing credit card processing and shipping fulfillment; fraud screening; testing and implementation of special services such as those for contacting members to offer personal, one-on-one, nutritional and member support to help members to reach their goals; and developing applications for this website and email services. These outside contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on our website, including your personal information, in the course of providing products or services to us. Access to your personal information by these outside contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the outside contractors to perform their limited function for us.

**Disclosure to Third Party Sellers**

Through this website, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or to obtain more information) regarding certain content, products or services which are sold through a person or company other than Organic Liaison. We will attempt to notify you when you are dealing with a third-party seller by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving our website. Third-party sellers may request that you submit certain personal information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. If you should make a purchase of these products or services, we will transmit your purchase data and your personal information to the third party seller so that the transaction can be processed.

If you do not wish for a third-party seller to have access to your personal information, please do not make purchases on this website. By making such purchases and submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the third-party seller. This information is used by the third-party seller and may be subject to a different privacy policy.

**Disclosure to Linked Sites**

For your convenience there may be links on our website to websites operated by companies other than Organic Liaison that are not contractors who provide content or services through this website. These links may be found in advertisements, referenced within content, or placed beside the names or logos of sponsors. Organic Liaison does not disclose your personal information to these third-party websites without obtaining your consent. In addition, Organic Liaison does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites. If you choose to link to one of these third party websites, you should thoroughly review the privacy policy posted on the other website.

#### SECURITY; PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

Keeping your personally identifiable information secure is very important to us. Thus, we strive to provide secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers and once we have received the information through generally accepted industry standards.

Even though we strive to protect your information, including your personally identifiable information, from loss, misuse, or alternation by third parties, you should note that there is no 100% secure method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage. Thus, while as stated above, we strive to protect your information using commercially acceptable means, we cannot guarantee absolute security, therefore information you provide to us is done so at your own risk.

#### CHILDREN

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. This website is not designed for, nor is it intended to attract, children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information directly from any person under the age of 13, and if we do inadvertently collect information from a person under the age of 13, we delete it as soon as we discover it.

#### PUBLIC FORUMS

This Privacy Policy does NOT protect you when you use our public forums. At these public forums, users may interact with one another and may share information, including, if you desire, personally identifiable information. You should be aware that any information shared in a public forum (such as chat rooms, bulletin boards, or your personal page) is public information and may be seen, disclosed to, or collected by third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy.

#### YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will only use personally identifiable information for the purposes described above or as otherwise disclosed at the time we request such information from you. You must "opt-in" and give us permission to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may notify us by calling us at 1 (800) 513-5201 or by contacting our Privacy Coordinator at the address set out below. You may change your preference and "opt-out" of receiving other communications by changing that option in your registration information on this website, or by contacting our Privacy Coordinator at the address set out below.

In addition, as noted above, you may "opt-out" of certain data tracking practices by our advertising partners. For more information about the data tracking practices of various third-party advertising companies, including their privacy practices and "opt-out" procedures, please go to the website operated by the Network Advertising Initiative at http://www.networkadvertising.org.

#### UPDATING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

You can always contact us in order to:

  * update or correct your personally identifiable information;
  * change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us; or
  * delete the personally identifiable information maintained about you on our systems.

You may do so by accessing your registration information on this website, or by contacting our Privacy Coordinator at the address set out below.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our systems. The need to back up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your personally identifiable information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. We promise that promptly after receiving your request, all personally identifiable information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable.

#### YOUR PRIVACY CONTACT AT Organic Liaison

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Coordinator:

  * by email at: legal@organicliaison.com or
  * by normal mail at: Organic Liaison  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel  
1465 S. Ft. Harrison Ave #206  
Clearwater, FL 33765
  * by telephone at: 1 (800) 513-5201

Organic Liaison will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
